{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680868839","data":{"timestamp":" 947680868839"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 5dc982d3-9e60-4d91-a043-637cf87079db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_mme-na-le"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" mme"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680876707","data":{"timestamp":" 947680876707"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 5dc982d3-9e60-4d91-a043-637cf87079db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_mme-na-le"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680886642","data":{"timestamp":" 947680886642"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 5dc982d3-9e60-4d91-a043-637cf87079db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_le-mwi-wu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680898218","data":{"timestamp":" 947680898218"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 5dc982d3-9e60-4d91-a043-637cf87079db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_le-lo-bu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680904661","data":{"timestamp":" 947680904661"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 5dc982d3-9e60-4d91-a043-637cf87079db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_la-da-le"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680911463","data":{"timestamp":" 947680911463"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 5dc982d3-9e60-4d91-a043-637cf87079db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_le-nje-to"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" nje"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680916971","data":{"timestamp":" 947680916971"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 5dc982d3-9e60-4d91-a043-637cf87079db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_le-nje-to"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680922278","data":{"timestamp":" 947680922278"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 5dc982d3-9e60-4d91-a043-637cf87079db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_be-mgo-le"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680926852","data":{"timestamp":" 947680926852"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 5dc982d3-9e60-4d91-a043-637cf87079db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_vu-le-mji"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680931383","data":{"timestamp":" 947680931382"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 5dc982d3-9e60-4d91-a043-637cf87079db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_le-nde-kwi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680937615","data":{"timestamp":" 947680937615"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 5dc982d3-9e60-4d91-a043-637cf87079db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_ng'i-mtu-le"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680942697","data":{"timestamp":" 947680942697"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 5dc982d3-9e60-4d91-a043-637cf87079db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_ha-le-da"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680948432","data":{"timestamp":" 947680948431"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 5dc982d3-9e60-4d91-a043-637cf87079db"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_le_ha-le-da"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680961168","data":{"timestamp":" 947680961168"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 488ada51-3c2b-42ef-8b3e-97e1ea18741b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680961402","data":{"timestamp":" 947680961402"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 488ada51-3c2b-42ef-8b3e-97e1ea18741b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680962379","data":{"timestamp":" 947680962378"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 488ada51-3c2b-42ef-8b3e-97e1ea18741b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680963675","data":{"timestamp":" 947680963674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 488ada51-3c2b-42ef-8b3e-97e1ea18741b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680966575","data":{"timestamp":" 947680966575"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 488ada51-3c2b-42ef-8b3e-97e1ea18741b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680967431","data":{"timestamp":" 947680967430"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 488ada51-3c2b-42ef-8b3e-97e1ea18741b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680967750","data":{"timestamp":" 947680967749"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 488ada51-3c2b-42ef-8b3e-97e1ea18741b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680968994","data":{"timestamp":" 947680968993"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 488ada51-3c2b-42ef-8b3e-97e1ea18741b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680972594","data":{"timestamp":" 947680972593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 488ada51-3c2b-42ef-8b3e-97e1ea18741b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680973592","data":{"timestamp":" 947680973591"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 488ada51-3c2b-42ef-8b3e-97e1ea18741b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680973852","data":{"timestamp":" 947680973851"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 488ada51-3c2b-42ef-8b3e-97e1ea18741b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680974808","data":{"timestamp":" 947680974807"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 488ada51-3c2b-42ef-8b3e-97e1ea18741b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680977715","data":{"timestamp":" 947680977715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 488ada51-3c2b-42ef-8b3e-97e1ea18741b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680978759","data":{"timestamp":" 947680978758"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 488ada51-3c2b-42ef-8b3e-97e1ea18741b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680979240","data":{"timestamp":" 947680979239"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 488ada51-3c2b-42ef-8b3e-97e1ea18741b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680983783","data":{"timestamp":" 947680983781"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 488ada51-3c2b-42ef-8b3e-97e1ea18741b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947680983896","data":{"timestamp":" 947680983896"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_154039"," gameId":" 488ada51-3c2b-42ef-8b3e-97e1ea18741b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}